Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of art Womens Committee records, circa 1960-2001 COR0008.1.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Trips, 1973-1992; Series 9
  - Northern Italy September 28 - October 15, 1984, 1984 September 28 - October 15; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - The Art and Architecture of Caracas November 12-19, 1988, 1988 November 12-19; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Art and Archeology Egypt February 16-28, 1989, 1989 February 16-28; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Providence, Newport and Boston May 31 - June 6, 1991, 1991 May 31 - June 6; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Loose Correspondence 1985, Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Minutes of the Meeting 1989, Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Event Photos, Undated; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Brunch October 11, 1992, 1992 October 11; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Files and Administration, Undated; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Loose Photos, Undated; Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Asia Trip 1979 (1 of 2), Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Asia Trip 1979 (2 of 2), Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Europe Trip 1981 (1 of 2), Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Europe Trip 1981 (2 of 2), Series 9 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Tour of Scandanavia July 30 - August 16, 1981, 1981 July 30 - August 16; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - China Trip April 28 - May 20, 1982, 1982 April 28 - May 20; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Paris and Environs Trip October 22 - Nov. 2, 1983, 1983 October 22 - November 2; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Paris Trip March 10-18, 1984, 1984 March 10-18; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles, Dallas, Ft. Worth, and Houston June 1-10, 1987, 1987 June 1-10; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Southern Italy Tour September 26 - October 11, 1987, 1987 September 26 - October 11; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Royal Viking Cruise August 20 - Sept. 6, 1989, 1989 August - September 6; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Bechhoefer Correspondence 1987, Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Rembrandt Edu. Tour June 12 - June 17, 1991, 1991 June 12-17; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Tour of Mexico Oct. 24 - Nov. 4, 91, 1991 October - November 4; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Misc 1985-1995, Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Russia / Scandinavia Cruise Program 1985, Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Yugoslavia and Budapest 1987-1988, Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Scandinavian Tour July 30 - August 16, 1981, 1981 July 30 - August 16; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Tour of New Mexico / Grand Canyon May 23 - June 1, 1985, 1985 1985 May 23 - June 1; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Dublin and the Irish Countryside August 17-25, 1988, 1988 August 17-25; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Tour of Montana and Minneapolis May 5-13, 1989, 1989 May 5-13; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Friends 1973-1977, Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Letters about Leon Smith, Jean Arp, and Fangor. 1971-1980, Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Georgia O'Keefe correspondence in 1977, 79, 1980, 1977-1980; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence for Italy trip - 1984, Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Corcoran Trip to Paris, for Nat'l - Council members, Trustees and Fellows (opening of L'Amour Fa) April 9-17, 1986, 1986 April 9-17; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Friends of the Corcoran Prague - Budapest Trip Nov. 3-10, 1977, 1977 November 3-10; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Friends of the Corcoran: Brazil Trip Oct. 30, 1977 - Nov. 8, 1977 October 30 - November 8; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Friends of the Corcoran Russian Trip - agreements Nov. 24 - Dec. 2, 1976, 1976 November 24 - December 2; Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneouus 1975-1985, Series 9 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Scrapbooks, 1940-1963; Series 10
  - Loose Documents, undated; Series 10 (Box 21A, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1940-1963; Series 10 (Box 21A, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook (Women's Committee), 1954-1960; Series 10 (Box 21B, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, undated; Series 10 (Box 21C, Folder 1)
- Janet Lundgren and Carolyn Amiot subject files, 1990-1995; Series 11
  - Ad Hoc Art Art Acquisition Report, 1992 January 21; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - 1993 Biennial Info, Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Develp.Committee, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Sept. Chairman's Letter to WC JAP, Moved, JML, 1992 September 1; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Old Core Annual Reportts Fr. Jan Brennan, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Mailing Labels Corcoran W.C., Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 1992-1994 Education Trips Report, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Corcoran Membership - by laws, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Museum Shop, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Program, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Project Evaluation, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - VCAM, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - May 1994 Minutes, 1994 May; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Exec. Minutes April 1994 WC, 1994 April; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - March 1994 W.C. Meeting + Exec. Com., 1994 March; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Feb. 1994 W.C. Meeting Notes Agendas Exec. Com., 1994 February; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - January 1994 Exec. W.C Meeting Agenda 7 Notes, 1994 January; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Sept. 1993 W.C. Mailings, 1993 September; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - September 93 Exec. W.C. Meeting, Agenda, Notes, etc. September 1993, 1993 September 28; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Agenda 9/28 W.C. 1993 Sept. Minutes + Executive, Com, Minutes, 1993 September 28; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Nov. 1993 Exec. + W.C. Agenda, Notes etc., 1993 November; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - October 1993 W.C. + Exec. Notes, Agenda etc, 1993 October; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Sept. 1993 Mailing from maryy Roddy to W.C. Exec. Com., 1993 September; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - May 1993 Exec. W.C. Mtg. Agenda, Notes etc., 1993 May; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - April 93 W.C. Exeec. Mtg. Minutes; May Meeting Notice Luncheon, 1993 April; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - May 1993 Exec. Com. + W.C. Minutes, 1993 May; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - April 1993 W.C. Agenda + Meeting Notes + Exec. Mtg. Agenda, 1993 April; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - March 1993 + Past W.C. Minutes, Exec. Com., Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Feb. 1993 Exec. Com notes, 1993 February; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - February 1993 Mailing Minutes, Ball Addressing + Agenda - Exec. Com. + W.C. Minutes, 1993 February; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Jan. 26, 1993 W.C. Meeting Agenda, Notes etc. Mailings, 1993 January 26; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Nov. 92 Mailing, Minutes Agenda Other Nov. Papers, 1992 November; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - October 27, 1992 Board W.C., 1992 October 27; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Janet 9/92 Mailing, 1992 September; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - 10/92 Mailing, 1992 October; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Sept. 1992 W.C., 1992 September; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - May 19, 1992 W.C. Meeting, 1992 May 19; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - June 1993 Exec. Com. June '90, '91, 1993 June; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - WC 1993-94 Calendar drafts + Final, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - National Committee, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Guidelines for Committee Chairs, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Corcoran BOT Sept. 26, 1994, 1994 September 26; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Corcoran BOT November 29, 1994, 1994 November 29; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Corcoran BOT January 30, 1995, 1995 January 30; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Board of Trustees; Board of Overseers - Lust / Names + Addresses, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Capital Campaign Committee, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Corcoran Aspen Institute 1994, Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Draft Future of Urban Museums 1994, Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Corcoran Financial Statements, 1993-1994; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - CSA Open Program/ Division of Continuing Education Spring Semester 1995, Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Corcoran Night Day Winter 1995, Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Corcoran Night Day March/April 1995, 1995 March-April; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Corcoran Financial Statements 1993-1994, Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - CSA Open Program/Division of Continuing Education Spring Semester 1995, Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Corcoran Night Day Winter 1995, Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Corcoran Night Day march/April 1995, 1995 March-April; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Board - Exec. Comm. 1994, Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Budget Expenses, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Corcoran Annual Meeting BOT 1995, 1995 May 22; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Corcoran Table of Contents 1995, Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - CGA Table of Contents FY'96, 1995; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Sheridan Group Packet 1995, Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Proposal of Service CGA 1995, Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Brakeley, Packet, Circa 1990-1999; Series 11 (Box 13, Folder 64)
- Jeannette Petite and Maud Brown subject files, 1988-1992; Series 12
  - Women's Committee Budget, 1989; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Beautification, 1989; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Corcoran Friends, 1989; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Loose Notes, 1989; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Special Arrangements, 1989; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Corcoran School, 1989; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Public Relations Brochure, 1989; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Programs/Hospitality, 1989; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Project Evaluation, 1989; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Memorial Committee, 1988; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Corcoran Ball Loose 1990, Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Cookbook, 1988; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Dudley Lecture, 1988; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Salon Dore and Loose Documents, 1990-1992; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Press, 1990; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Art Acquisitions, 1990-1992; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Dean Resignation, 1991; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - 1991 Corcoran Ball, Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Beautification/Holiday, 1991; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - By-Laws, Circa 1980-1999; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1992; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Memorial for Jane Wyeth, 1991; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - French Room, Circa 1980-1999; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Membership New Member Advisory, Circa 1980-1999; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Dudley Lecture, 1991; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Report, 1988-1990; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Gifts/Budget, 1990; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Minutes, 1989 March; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Programs/Hospitality/Education/Gifts, Circa 1980-1999; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Public Relations, 1991; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Shop, Circa 1980-1999; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - VCAM, Circa 1980-1999; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Loose Women's Committee, Circa 1980-1999; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Development Committee, 1990; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Friends, Circa 1980-1999; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Leadership Strategy, Circa 1980-1999; Series 12 (Box 12, Folder 36)